Contact

christin.zink@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/christinzink-5aab25ba (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Critical Care Rapid Response Medical-Surgical

Languages

English (Native or Bilingual)

Christin Zink

BSN, RN, CCRN, UNF CRNA class of 2021

Jacksonville, Florida Area

Summary

Hardworking professional who is always open to a new challenge. I have had the pleasure to work at one of Virginia/Maryland/and Washington DC's top level 1 trauma centers since graduating nursing school in 2011, INOVA Fairfax Hospital. I started in the Medical Surgical ICU and completed the New Graduate Critical Care Fellowship program in my first four months. While at INOVA Fairfax, I worked in the MICU, CCU, Neuro ICU, CVICU, and Trauma ICU. I gained knowledge and hands on experience with a variety of patients that included EVDs, bolts, CRRT, cardiac surgery patients and fresh traumas.

After working with INOVA Health Systems for almost 5yrs I moved to Tampa, Florida and worked at Tampa General CTICU and then went to work for Baycare Health Systems Mobile Pool in Critical Care. With Baycare I worked at 13 acute care hospitals in a variety of ICUs in the Tampa/St. Petersburg area.

Currently I am enrolled in the University of North Floridas Nurse Anesthesia Program in Jacksonville, FL with an expected graduation date in December 2021.

Experience

BayCare Health System Critical Care Registered Nurse May 2016 - April 2019 (3 years) Tampa, Florida

Mobile Pool Critical Care RN serving 13 acute care hospitals in Tampa, FL Currently at Morton Plant Hospital MSICU in Clearwater 3/2018-6/2018

Tampa General Hospital
CVICU Registered Nurse
November 2015 - May 2016 (7 months)

Page 1 of 2

Inova Health System
Critical Care Registered Nurse
July 2011 - November 2015 (4 years 5 months)
Falls Church, Virginia

2.5 years experience as a new graduate in the Medical-Surgical ICU after completing a 4 month Critical Care Fellowship program
I then did 2.5 years doing ICU Float Pool RN in which I floated to 6 different Intensive Care Units (CCU, CVICU, TICU, NSICU, MSICU, and Intermediate Care)

Fairfax County Park Authority Manager 2005 - June 2011 (6 years) Chantilly, VA

Worked as a building Manager on Duty at CubRun RECenter as well as the Watermine Waterpark.

- -I managed the daily allocation of monies and safe deposits of the Front Desk sales as well as planning and executing the schedule and training for all Front Desk staff.
- -Assisted in helping customers with membership and facility related questions.
- -Helped evaluate and resolve customer complaints

Education

University of North Florida

Doctorate, Nurse Anesthetist (2019 - 2021)

George Mason University

Bachelor's degree, Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse · (2008 - 2011)

East Tennessee State University Undergraduate · (2006 - 2008)